Hello friends, how are you all? Log in.
Thanks for watching my channel. Friends,
before starting the video, I request you to
subscribe to the channel and
also press the notification button so that
whenever I upload a new video, you get
notified. So friends, let's start the video
and in this video we will
talk about a strange company. Its legacy
is very strong and this is general insurance. Does it belong to the
insurance sector? The
name of this company is ICICI Lombard.
ICICI Lombard General Insurance.
Now, look, this is insurance. So, even though it has been
listed for three-four years, the
thing is that this
business is reducing in subscriptions. But in a country like India,
all this business is not big. If you
think that its growth in the long term is
very good and it is going to be big,
then no doubt about it, because of the
way it is concentrated,
in that case, you will see that the insurance sector is going to be a
big sector because whoever
wants his own things, he can leave other things
and keep them. Subscribe to
my channel here.  Don't forget to subscribe
Meghwal folds it, any
business in any of these sectors, any industry, that is
one thing and the share price is
another thing, keep this in mind because
if you look at it in general, if you
talk about the juice add number of this company right now, then its
validation is so high, 5550 times,
in the middle of it, its please
comes here that it is
subscribed for a product like insurance, the first and
second thing is that everyone
knows about its business model, everyone
knows about it, we subscribed like in
2008,
and many were banned by the government,
and this was the experience from where
we came to know that there can be a risk on insurance,
but they should subscribe to our channel, on the
other hand, the
demographics of the mother company
and the pending pattern you keep is completely different,
so we can land it on the basis of the country,
Rabbit, here you will have to look at all this also
and even the share price,
remember one thing, it says outside,
you have bought from a good company because  Its
brand like Apple's Village branded
domestically is a big brand and Nobel Price, so now
look, there is only one brand, there is a business, but when it comes to
validation, right, I will
also buy the share price in a good company
when there will be sex workers, when there will be schools,
like look here, I went into subscription
because see here, 40 percent
reservation was done in two months, but it is fast, so
here it shows
how much consumer confidence in Mr. Especially all these
products are
a bird, this is such a set of skin news,
before talking about this, let me tell you something, this is such a chapter
which is still involving, so you
take any decision, if it is coming on TV,
saying that it is good for the long term, then
that is fine, you
can read that report, but you are
buying for the purpose, this thing should be
clear, bread 100, here we
start,
so look here, I am giving you support lines from that
here basically and there is
such a divide in the charter and process, okay, now
we will do this  You will see the candy stick, it
is divided into phases and what you will see is that above you see
4000 thirteen here, so here
you see
that it is around 1450 and below you
see here thousand sixteen, so the
range of this chart point is a consolidating
ranger, power ranger, but remember one thing that it is
important that it has come from here to here,
then it can be done here, it is
important that after this it will start directly, it is being
said, so you will be very careful about
this thing, you can be strict about this,
consolidate, I
could not talk about it, so
here we try to throw a big trend, so
this food also something like this,
see, it has happened here, after
seeing this, you will
see something like this here, you will
see something like this here, and
if it crosses here, then the
resistance level on it is around 1658, so
this is a big train,
see here it is a big train
and it is above the line  Voting was suspended
above the soil, so where did you touch it,
now is it 05 or 2000, it is special, this
time it is tight, but see here, if
I do not do it above this, then it can
consolidate in this range, let us ask,
this thing is also worth understanding here
and the number here, suppose if it gets
pregnant with this line,
then here it
can touch the line from 200 to 350, but this
is in your mouth and
what kind of direction will it have in the North Market, that it depends on the
demand-supply, share price,
business, but not on the momentum and mood,
so
friends, if you liked the video, then like and share it
and tell us by writing in the comment section
and not only this, but also subscribe to the channel for more content,
real take care friends